社区中心不仅仅是一个健身场所
And Community Play is about more than just providing gyms.
还是联接执法部门和危险少年
It's about building bridges between law enforcement
之间的桥梁
and at-risk kids.
孩子们能在这里了解
It's a place where kids get to know
警徽背后的人
the person behind the badge.
警察不用抓人  问话
And police aren't making arrests and asking questions.
他们可以传达他们的领导技巧
Instead they're giving their perspectives on leadership,
应对冲突手段和热情
conflict resolution, empathy,
最重要的是  信任
and most importantly, trust.
社区中心需要你们这样的好人
Community Play thrives on good folks like you.
我说的好人
And when I say good folks,
是指热心有干劲
I mean caring, compassionate people
并愿意解囊相助的人
who are also willing to open those wallets.
今晚早些时候  我在北边
You know, earlier tonight I was taking a little walk
风景宜人的街道上散步
on beautiful streets here on the North Side.
这是我们都想看到的芝加哥
This is the Chicago we all want.
其乐融融  没有枪支暴力的避风港
Family friendly. A safe haven from gun violence.
在你们的帮助  我们已经让这个组织
And with your help, we've made this little organization
也成为了避风港
a safe haven as well.
所以谢谢你们今晚的到来  上帝保佑
So thank you for coming tonight, and God bless.
谢谢你们
Thank you.
我们走吧  去好好喝一杯
Yo, let's get out of here and get a real drink.
凡妮莎和乔丹最近怎么样
Hey, how are Vinessa and Jordan doing?
他们挺好的
They're actually doing pretty good.
不过我和他们说了  他们要是成为牛仔队粉丝
I told 'em though, if they become Cowboys fans,
就不用回来了
they can't come back.
-有可能吗  -你想走了吗
- Is that a possibility? - You wanna roll?
我们十分钟后下班
We're off the clock in ten minutes.
除非你还知道有别的地方
Unless you know another place
免费提供拉罗克红酒
serving free Chantal de Laroque?
你真是...怎么说的来着
Wow. You're really um... Oh what's the word?
势利
Le snob.
我的莱克福里斯特特质
The Lake Forest in me escaping.
什么  我以为你是希腊城的
What? I thought you were from Greektown.
那只是我在酒吧瞎编的
That's just a story I tell in bars.
我开玩笑的
Just kidding.
我十一岁的时候我们家搬到那里
We moved there when I was 11.
你认识那个人吗
You know that guy?
嗯  肖恩·麦克格雷迪  缉毒部警长
Yeah. Sean McGrady. Sergeant out of narcotics.
几年前
Couple years back
我被派和他进行过联合调查
I was assigned to his joint investigation.
好警察一个
Good police.
她的语气有所迟疑
She says with hesitation.
不  他的确不错  他只是...
No, he is. He's just--
很好胜  总会想办法攀比  把我逼疯
Competitive. Always looking for an angle. Drove me nuts.
汉克  很高兴你来
Hank! Glad you came.
谢谢你和你的小队
I appreciate all the time and effort
为这里所花的时间和精力
your team has put in around here.
都是为了做好事  乐意帮忙
It's a good cause. Happy to help.
真是一场盛大的宴会
It's a hell of a shindig.
要赚钱就得先花钱
Well, you got to spend money to make money.
肖恩  我们得谈谈
Sean, we need to talk about this!
原创翻译  双语字幕
-你想谈谈  -没错  就今晚
- Oh you want to talk? - Yeah. Tonight!
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
你想现在谈谈吗
You want to talk about this now?
你是疯了吗
What, are you out of your mind?
-怎么回事  -我们没事
- What's going on? - No, we're good.
翻译     小酸奶   西之   风城章鱼X
对吧  我们没事
Right? We're good.
很高兴见到你  海莉
It's good to see you, Hailey.
翻译     不高兴童鞋   H小欠   圈圈
你没事吧
You okay?
没事  只是一点误会
Yeah. It was just a misunderstanding.
校对     圈圈
附近发生枪击案
We got shots fired nearby.
时间轴     西查   chance-coco
-枪手在逃  -好
- Active shooter. - Okay.
后期     8T
总监     圈圈
-我去  -楼梯
- I've got it. - Stairs.
两人倒下
I got two down!
掩护我
Cover me.
-怎么样  -都死了
- Anything? - They're both gone.
他还有脉搏  快叫救护车
He got a pulse. Call an ambo.
5021C  马上派一辆救护车来
This is 5021 Charlie. Roll an ambo to our location.
3人中枪  一人尚有呼吸
3 GSWs, one still breathing.
九毫米  男性脑后中了一枪
Nine mil casings. Male takes one to the back of the head.
女性胸口中了两枪
Female takes two to the chest.
父亲先被打  然后中枪
Dad gets beat, then popped.
妻子走进来  一起被灭口
Wife walks in. Goodbye witness.
儿子瑞安  躲在厕所里
Son Ryan, he's hiding out in the bathroom.
杀手找到了他  他当胸中了两枪
Killer finds him. He takes two to the chest.
查出死者身份了吗
Anything on the victims yet?
格兰特·汉蒙德  妻子玛格瑞特  儿子瑞安
Yeah. Grant Hammond, wife Margaret, son Ryan.
格兰特是一名公司律师
Grant was a corporate attorney.
他好像会在教堂花很多时间
Looks like he spent a lot of time at his church.
我觉得我们找到凶手
Hey. I think we found what the killers
在楼上找什么了
were looking for upstairs.
赞美上帝
Praise the Lord.
两公斤  市值得有二十万
Two keys. That's about 200 grand street value.
我见过因为比这更少的毒品杀人的家伙
I've seen guys kill over a lot less.
看来北区不是什么避风港了
So much for the safe haven of the North Side.
芝加哥
警署
第五季
第六集
米娅来电
米娅  新交往的妹子吗  伙计
Oh, Mia, huh? You got a new honey, Dawg?
一夜情还差不多
It was more like a one night acquaintance.
晚上好  女士  我是我是鲁塞克警官
Good evening, ma'am. I'm Officer Ruzek,
-这是阿特沃特警官  -我正准备打给你们
- this is Officer Atwater, we-- - I was about to call you.
这种开场白可不常见
Oh. We don't get that a lot.
-你看到什么了吗  -我本来在厨房
- Did you see something? - I was in the kitchen.
刚开始我听到了喊叫声  然后三下很响的枪声
At first I heard shouting, then three loud pops.
我去窗户边想看看  几秒种后  一个人跑了
I went to the window, and a few seconds later, a man ran out.
那个人看上去长什么样
Okay. What does this man look like?
他很高...深色皮肤
He was tall. Um...dark skinned.
-黑人  -没错
- Black? - Yes.
他戴了帽子  我看不清他的脸
He had a hat on. I couldn't really see his face.
他跑进一辆黑色的车子开走了
He got into a black SUV. Drove away.
-一切发生得太快  -好吧
- It happened so fast. - Okay.
你是汉蒙德一家的朋友吗
Were you friends with the Hammonds?
-你和他们熟吗  -嗯  我们是朋友
- Did you know them well? - Yeah. Yeah, we were friends.
他和玛格瑞特两周前还来我家吃晚饭
He and Margaret were over two weeks ago for dinner.
好的  他们有提到过什么吗
Okay. Did they mention anything?
和别人有什么过节吗
Have any problems with anyone?
不  不  他们都是精英人士
No. No, they were on top of the world.
他们很为自己的儿子瑞安而感到自豪
They were so proud of Ryan, their son.
总是说他在耶鲁有多么棒
How well he was doing at Yale.
我看到瑞安躺在担架上被抬走了
I saw Ryan taken out on a stretcher.
他没事吧
Is he okay?
我们现在只知道他还活着
As far as we know he's alive.
他现在正在芝加哥医院进行手术
He's in surgery right now at Chicago Med.
晚安  谢谢
Have a good night. Thank you.
目前还没有摄像头或监控
So far no surveillance or PODS
拍到枪手
caught sight of the shooter.
对格兰特·汉蒙德的调查有发现吗
Anything on Grant Hammond?
他资产被没收  并被发布了联名声明
Asset Forfeiture, they ran the round robin on him.
他破产了  得还五张信用卡的卡债
He was broke, he was juggling five credit cards.
他之前的雇主
Hasn't received a check
一年多没给他发过工资了
from his last employer in over a year.
是他的律所  去年把他开除了
That would be his law firm. They let him go last year.
他的银行账户里有什么存款吗
Okay. Any cash deposits to his bank account?
没有  他比较聪明
No, he was a little smarter than that.
用的是保险箱
He was using a safety deposit box,
但是银行因为他经常光顾而开始进行安全分析报告
but the bank filled out an SAR on him for frequent visits.
所以说他是在
Okay, so he is dealing on the side
走投无路的边缘
to make ends meet.
或者是为了保持完美的生活
Or to keep up his perfect lifestyle.
奢华的上流生活  上大学的孩子
Fancy brownstone. Kid in college.
伙计们  我觉得我找到供应商了
Guys, I think I have a lead on the supplier.
不错的切入点
Good place to start.
技术员查看了汉蒙德车上的GPS
Techs ran GPS on Hammond's car.
他去过很多次恩格尔伍德
He'd been making multiple trips to Englewood.
-查到地址了吗  -拉辛南街6341号
- Got an address? - 6241 South Racine.
藏匿点在一个叫做昆顿·凯恩的人名下
Stash house is linked to a Quinton Kane.
显然是个惯犯
Apparently he's a pretty serious player.
通过黄金海岸运送了很多毒品
Moves a lot of product through the Gold Coast.
好  去查一下凯恩
All right. Get the details on Kane,
让人去盯一下
then get some eyes on him.
你可能要联系一下缉毒队的麦克格雷迪
Oh, you should probably contact McGrady in Narcotics.
那里是他的队的地盘
His team covers that area.
警长
Sarge?
这样人有点多了
Makes for a crowded van.
你是说你和麦克格雷迪有过节吗
You saying you got a problem with McGrady?
对
Yeah.
自己解决  这是你的工作
Well, work it out. You got a job to do.
就像以前一样
Oh, this seems like old times.
我知道我们以前有过节
Look I know we've had our differences,
但我们还是专注工作吧
but let's just focus on the job.
专业一点  好吗
Keep it professional, okay?
好吧
Yeah.
昆顿·凯恩有什么信息可以分享
So what do we know about Quinton Kane?
我正在查的三起谋杀案
Well, he's a main suspect in three homicides
他都是主要嫌疑人
that I've been chasing.
就快抓到他了  但是没有起诉
We get close, but you know, no indictment
都是因为勇敢的助理检察官
thanks to the brave ASAs.
-知道他是哪个帮的吗  -知道  一百辛迪加
- You know what flag he flies? - Yeah. It's the 100 Syndicate.
他还有一些合法的生意
He has a couple of legit businesses too.
-前科呢  -两项
- Any priors? - Mm-hmm. Two.
五年前暴力殴打他人  三个月前醉驾
Five years ago agg battery. And then three months ago DUI.
案子还没结
Case still pending.
我想这么做
Listen this is how I want to run it, all right?
我主要盯人  海莉你负责记录
I'm gonna take the main eye. Hailey, you handle the log.
杰  你去收集照片和视频
Jay, I want you to do stills and video,
我们要证明凯恩搞的是
'cause we want to prove that it's an open-air market
合法买卖  好吗  行动
that Kane's running, all right? Let's go.
节哀顺变  瑞安
We're so sorry for your loss, Ryan.
对  医生说你做得很好
Yeah. The doctor says you're doing great.
昨晚的事你还记得什么吗
Do you remember anything about last night?
一些事
A few things.
慢慢来
Take it slow.
你和父母一起吃了饭
All right, you had dinner with your parents?
对
Yeah.
我回了房间
I went to my bedroom.
我刚下飞机比较累
I was tired from my flight.
和朋友视频了
I was FaceTiming with a friend.
然后我听到门铃响
Then I heard the door buzz.
我爸让谁进来了
My dad let someone in.
我听到了争吵声
I heard arguing.
你爸爸在等人吗
Was your dad expecting anyone?
-没有  -你认得那个人的声音吗
- No. - Did you recognize the voice?
不认识
No.
他一直在大喊
He kept yelling,
"不是这样的"
"This ain't how it works."
-然后呢  -我就听到了枪声
- What happened next? - I heard gunshots.
-我不知道该怎么办  -没事的
- I didn't know what to do. - It's okay.
我跑到卫生间躲了起来
I ran towards my bathroom... to hide.
遭到了枪击
I got hit.
瑞安...
Ryan...
你看到开枪打你的人了吗
did you see the man who shot you?
他来了
There he is.
我能看看吗
Can I-- Can I see it?
没错  是他
Oh, hell, yeah. Yeah
左边的是昆顿·凯恩
The guy on the left, that's Quinton Kane.
一个冷血杀手
He's a stone cold killer.
和他在一起的人是贝纳德·沃德  人称"贝贝"
The guy with him is Bernard Ward, AKA "Bay Bay."
就是那辆黑色SUV  和邻居说的一样
That's the black SUV. Just like the neighbor said.
很好  我想是时候
Great. Well I think it's time
和"公民凯恩"谈一谈了
that we should have a little chat with Citizen Kane.
我是霍斯特德
Halsted.
好  明白
Okay. Got it.
那个瑞安·汉蒙德刚刚指认说
The son Ryan Hammond, he just ID'd the shooter
枪手是一个纹着狗纹身的黑人
as a tall black man with some sort of dog tattoo
纹身在右前臂上
on his right forearm.
查一下文件
Check the file.
是凯恩  狗爪纹身
That's Kane. Dog claw.
是一百辛迪加的标志纹身
That's the 100 Syndicate initiation tattoo.
证据确凿  我们去抓他
That's good enough for me. Let's grab him up.
谢谢你来  昆顿
Thanks for coming in, Quinton.
你和格兰特·汉蒙德很熟吗
So how well do you know Grant Hammond?
格兰特什么
Grant who?
别把我当白痴  昆顿
Don't disrespect me like that, Quinton.
他的快速拨号是你  他曾是你黄金海岸的联系人
He had you on speed dial. He was your Gold Coast connect,
有很多人都说
and we got a lot of people whispering around here
他为你贩毒
saying he's running dope for you.
那个格兰特·汉蒙德啊
Oh, that Grant Hammond.
不  他只是给我提供法律建议
No. He just gives me legal advice.
-我现在很配合吧  -那很好
- See I'm incorporated now. - Well good for you.
昨晚你在哪
So where were you last night?
你要告诉我到底发生什么事了吗
You gonna tell me what this is about?
-我还有别的地方要去  -没有了
- I got places to be. - Well not anymore.
怎么  你不认得他吗  瑞安·汉蒙德  19岁
What? You don't recognize him? Ryan Hammond? 19?
你昨晚用枪打中了他的胸口
Come on. You shot him in the chest last night.
就这里
Right there.
你猜怎么着
Guess what?
结果这孩子很坚强
It turns out that this kid is a fighter.
他活下来了
He survived.
他刚刚指认你就是枪手
And he just ID'd you as the shooter.
-我没开枪打任何人  -昆顿  拜托
- I didn't shoot no one. - Quinton. Come on.
我在给你活路呢
I'm throwing you a lifeline here.
我在给你机会说话
I'm giving you a chance to tell your side of the story.
说啊  好吧  我来帮你
Come on. All right. I'll help you out.
他欠你钱  不是  我知道了
He owed you money. No, I got it. Right.
是他朝你开枪  你只是在正当防卫
He shot at you, and you were just defending yourself.
-这个借口不错  -对
- That's a really good one. - Mm.
我被捕了吗
Am I under arrest?
你可以走
You're free to go.
两具尸体  一个濒死的大学生
Two dead bodies, a dying college kid,
结果我们要放了凯恩
and we got to kick Kane free
就因为瑞安·汉蒙德的指认太模糊
because Ryan Hammond's ID is too vague.
是啊  很幸运我们该得到的都得到了
Yeah, well, we're lucky we got what we got when we got it.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我刚和医院联系过  瑞安·汉蒙德十分钟前去世了
I just talked to Med. Ryan Hammond died 10 minutes ago.
他才19岁  刚刚从学校回家
He's 19 years old. He's just back home from college.
没有瑞安的证词  我们无法指控凯恩
Without Ryan's testimony, we don't have a case against Kane.
所以那个混蛋可能会逍遥法外
So that son of a bitch might actually get away with it.
我们要回头去找新的证据
We just gotta get back out there, find new evidence.
-你和麦克格雷迪谈过了吗  -对  刚刚谈了
- Hey, did you talk to McGrady? - Yeah. I just talked to him.
他说今晚想一起讨论案情
He said he wants to meet up and go over the case tonight.
一起讨论案情
Meet up and go over the case?
他有新线索新证据吗
Did he bring up new leads, new evidence?
没有  他什么也没提
No. He didn't mention anything.
真的是讨论案子吗
Is this really about the case?
明天见
I'll see you tomorrow.
好吧
Okay.
请求支援  6245小组  警察中枪
Ten one! 6245 squad. Shot fired at the police.
我在霍因南路5392号  我中枪了  老天
I'm at 5392 South Hoyne. I've been hit! Oh God.
警察中枪  老天
Officer down! Oh, my God. Agh.
我是5021C  我现在去
This is 5021 Charlie. I'm en route
支援遇险警察
to the officer calling the ten one.
我出警  我离他五个街区远
I will respond. I'm five blocks away.
收到  收到  6245坚持住
Copy that. Copy that. 6245 hang in there.
我是5021C  我到现场了
5021 Charlie. I'm at the scene of the ten one.
收到  5021C
Copy that, 5021 Charlie.
麦克  麦克
Mac? Mac.
天啊  麦克  麦克
Oh God. Mac! Mac!
有警员受伤  重复  有警员受伤
I got an officer down! I repeat, officer down!
-请求立即增援  -收到
- Send me some help now! - Copy that.
坚持住  麦克  坚持住
Stay with me, Mac. Stay with me.
加油  坚持住  麦克  麦克
Come on. Come on. No, no, no, no. Mac! Mac!
麦克  麦克
Mac. Mac!
有什么最新进展
Yeah, so what's the latest?
我让南区  战术小队  帮派调查组
I got Area South, tact, gang,
和巡警队全员出动
and patrol officers out in full force,
挨家挨户搜索所有的逃跑路线和车库
going door to door searching every gangway and garage.
目前还没有凶手的踪迹  也没有目击证人
So far no sign of the offender, no witnesses.
你需要什么  就告诉我
Well, you tell me what you need, I'll make it happen.
我相信你  丹尼  但是不用了
I know you will, Denny. We're good.
听着  我知道大家都很着急
Okay, look. I know everyone is hot.
我们自己人被杀了
One of our very own was just killed.
但是有情报不能瞒着
But keep it on the up and up.
雷  多谢你来
Hey, Ray. Thanks for coming.
有什么需要帮忙的地方就告诉我
Any way I can help, just let me know.
我在街头安排了教堂的人
I have the church down the block.
接待你们的警员  咖啡和水尽管喝
It's open for your officers. Coffee and bottled water.
多谢  非常感激  失陪了
Hey, thanks. I appreciate that. Excuse me.
有线索吗
Any leads?
没什么确实的
Nothing solid.
也许和黄金海岸凶杀案有关联
Maybe connected to the Gold Coast murders.
你听着  被杀警官名叫麦克格雷迪
Listen. The slain officer's name was McGrady.
在查一条和昆顿·凯恩有关的线索
He was working a lead on Quinton Kane.
此人在你的选区里活动  听说过吗
Runs in your ward. You heard of him?
我知道他
I know the name.
是不是说他也资助了你的重建计划
That mean he helped finance your redevelopment projects?
我只是说我知道他
It means I know the name.
如果这个混蛋真的杀了一个警察
If this bastard killed a police officer,
一个和我共事  让我尊敬的人
a guy I worked with, a guy I respected,
那我希望你能完全配合
I expect your full cooperation.
那当然不用说
Goes without saying.
说吧
Talk to me.
显然情况是这样的  警长
Yeah, so apparently what happened, Sarge,
麦克格雷迪在车前座被人袭击
McGrady got jumped in the front seat of the vehicle,
然后双方一直在争夺他的枪
and then from there it was just a fight for his weapon.
凶手朝他开了两枪  一枪击中防弹背心
Offender shot him twice. One in the vest point blank,
一枪从脖子穿透出去
one in the neck, through and through.
就是这枪打碎了玻璃
That's what shattered the glass.
我们在枪上找到的唯一指纹就是麦克格雷迪的
The only prints we could find on the gun were McGrady's.
枪柄上还有血
There was blood on the grip of the gun.
已经把枪送到实验室去了
We sent the gun to the crime lab already.
也许只是一场当街抢劫
This might have just been a random robbery.
又或许是他和线人翻脸了
Or maybe he got into it with a CI?
那好  立即检查麦克格雷迪的手机
All right, so dump McGrady's phone right away.
确认过去24小时他联系过的所有人
Identify everyone he was in contact with the last 24 hours.
明白
Copy that.
-目击证人呢  -和和一个目击者谈过了
- Witnesses? - I talked to one witness.
说麦克格雷迪中枪20分钟前  在这建筑附
Saw a black SUV around the building about 20 minutes
近看见一辆黑色越野  驾驶员是黑人
before McGrady was shot. Black male behind the wheel.
-凯恩  -有可能
- Kane? - It's possible.
好吧  开始查吧
All right. So start digging.
查查这一切发生的时候他在哪
Find out where he was when this whole thing went down.
-你确定你没事吗  -我没事
- Are you sure you're okay? - Yeah. I'm okay.
杰  我单独和她说几句话
Hey, Jay, give me a second alone with her.
好的  警长  有需要就告诉我
Yeah. Sure, Sarge. Let me know if you need anything.
多谢
Thanks.
你肯定很难过  我很抱歉
Tough thing to go through. I'm sorry.
但我不得不问
But I gotta ask.
你为什么让麦克格雷迪独自行动
Why did you let McGrady drive in alone?
什么
Excuse me?
你本应该和他一起行动
You were supposed to be working with him.
我是和他一起
I was working with him.
他知道我要来  我们刚在电话上说过话
He knew I was coming. We just got off the phone.
-我让他等我  -等你喝完咖啡吗
- I told him to wait for me. - While you stopped for coffee?
他应该等着我
He was supposed to wait for me!
但是你来晚了
But you were late!
这不公平
That's not fair.
而且我没晚  我还早到了十分钟
And I wasn't late. I was ten minutes early.
他死了  海莉
He's dead, Hailey.
公不公平的我不在乎
I don't really care about fair.
节哀顺变
I'm so sorry.
如果有什么我能帮你的话...
If there's anything you need, anything I can do--
谢了
Thank you.
女士们
Ladies.
你不如去坐下歇会儿吧  去吃点东西
Why don't you go sit down? Have something to eat?
喝杯酒也行  好吗
Maybe a glass of wine, all right?
你能来很好  海莉  但我们这不需要什么
Nice of you to come by, Hailey, but I think we're good.
我正要去和他会合  阿诺德
I was on my way to meet him, Arnold.
但他决定提前行动了
He decided to go in early.
我现在不想谈这些事
I'd rather not discuss that now.
不要在这  在安的面前说
Not here. Not in front of Anne.
我知道你们两个搭档了很久
Look, I know you guys were partners for a long time.
你可曾听说过他这么单独行动过
You ever known him to go in solo like that?
没有
No.
他告诉我他要去见一个线人
He told me he was meeting a snitch
关于黄金海岸凶杀案的
about the Gold Coast murders--
我现在真的不想谈这件事
I don't want to discuss any of this now.
你赶紧走吧
Just get the hell out of here.
快走
Go.
就是这个
That's it?
警长  来听听这个
Hey, Sarge, you want to hear this.
-说  -我们查了麦克格雷迪的手机
- Okay. - We dumped McGrady's phone.
只查出了这个人最可疑
And this is the only cat that popped up.
一个还没登记的线人  叫戴蒙·布里格斯
An informant named Damon Briggs that wasn't on the books yet.
我和麦克格雷迪的搭档说过了
I spoke to McGrady's partner.
布里格斯曾因枪支犯罪被捕  后来放了
Briggs is a catch and release on a gun charge.
态度非常恶劣
Slinging a lot of attitude.
麦克格雷迪正打算把他关回监狱
McGrady was about to toss him back into prison.
上周这个人给麦克格雷迪打了三次电话
This man called McGrady three times over the last week,
而他中枪之前两个小时就在和他通话
and was on the phone with him two hours before he got popped.
那好  叫上霍斯特德  把布里格斯找来
All right. Grab Halsted, find this Briggs, bring him in.
不过也别放过凯恩  先挖掘一下
Let's not back off Kane though. Do some digging.
-查查他的不在场证据  -好的
- Check his alibi. - All right.
找你可不容易啊  戴蒙
You're a hard man to find, Damon.
你躲什么
Why you hiding?
天  我只是想活到周日早上
G, I'm just trying to see Sunday morning.
白人条子在我们那被杀
White cop killed in my hood.
偏偏我又和他有过节
I'm the brother beefin' with him.
我想想就猜到了
Yeah, I did the math.
你昨晚10点左右在哪里
Where were you last night, 10:00 p.m.?
我开车去威斯康星州了  轮胎好使
I drove to Wisconsin. Good for the tires.
加了油  马上就回来了
Got gas. Came right back.
不在场证明挺不错啊
Great alibi.
你最后和麦克格雷迪说话是什么时候
When was the last time you spoke with McGrady?
一两个月前  也就说了一分钟吧
A month. Two. Been a minute.
那你昨天打他的卧底用手机
What about when you called him yesterday
是说什么事情
on his undercover phone?
那是私事
Oh. That was personal.
我还以为你们在说正事
I thought y'all was talkin' business.
我借给他一千块钱  还没还我
I lent him a grand. Hadn't paid me back yet.
所以我们一直在吵架
You know that's why we was conflictin'.
我觉得他是惹着什么危险人物了
I think dude was in with some serious people.
明白我什么意思吧
Know what I'm saying?
他说他为什么需要钱了吗
Did he say why he needed the money?
还用说吗
He didn't have to.
我们大部分时间都在聊赌城的手气
We spent most of our time talking Vegas odds.
就我所知  他每场球赛都要赌一把
Far as I can tell, he wouldn't pass up a sports bet.
这老哥在赌小联盟比赛
Dude was betting on little league games.
不要出城  戴蒙  我们会再联系你
Stay in town, Damon. We'll be in touch.
我哪里都不会去的
I ain't going nowhere.
你相信他的话吗
You believe this guy?
-我信  -为什么
- I do. - Why?
钱的事  确实讲得通
The money thing. Makes sense.
麦克格雷迪上个月让我借他几千块钱
McGrady asked me to borrow a few grand last month.
你借他钱了
You lent him money?
我可没这么说  我只是说他找我了
I didn't say I lent him money. I said he asked.
听起来他好像状况确实不太好
He sounded like he was in a really bad place.
有多不好
How bad?
他喜欢赌博  还经常输
Well, he likes to gamble. And he loses a lot.
我们有很多可能的嫌疑人
There's a lot of potential suspects here.
好了  我们继续查一下
All right. Let's follow up
布里格斯所说的去威斯康辛的旅行
on Briggs' alleged trip to Wisconsin.
那个就是凯恩  吧台那头的那个
That's Kane. End of the bar.
说不定是另一天晚上的
This could be another night.
是啊  我奶奶都能用鼠标
Right. I mean, my grandma can click a mouse
改掉这玩意的日期
and change the date on this thing.
我什么都没改
I didn't change nothing.
他背后的电视上在播10点的新闻
That's the 10:00 news running behind him on the TV.
拜托你们去抓别的黑人吧
Do yourself a favor and find another black man to arrest.
凯恩就在这里
Kane was here.
是啊  在他自己的酒吧里  你那晚上班了吗
Right. In the bar he owns. Did you work that night?
上了  我看到他了
Yeah I did. I saw him.
我愿意在任何法官面前作证
And I'd testify to any judge you name.
你肯定是收了不少钱吧
I'm sure you'd be paid handsomely for it too.
祝你今晚愉快  帅哥
Have a good night, handsome.
昆顿·凯恩
在告密者布里格斯身上查到什么了吗
All right. What do we got on our snitch Briggs?
他确实是去威斯康辛旅游了
He totally was on a joy ride going to scenic Wisconsin.
信用卡账单和加油站监控显示
Credit card receipts, gas station surveillance
麦克格雷迪被杀的时候他正在
puts him at a Kenosha gas station at the same time
基诺沙的一个加油站
McGrady was shot.
好吧  那就把布里格斯的名字划掉
All right, so cross Briggs off the list.
凯恩的事查的怎么样了
Where are we at with Kane?
警长  凯恩的不在场证明没问题
Sarge, Kane's alibi checks out.
是啊  我们在监控视频上看到
Yeah, we got Kane on surveillance video
凯恩10点21进入了酒吧
at 10:21 entering the dive bar.
那酒吧是他自己的  你确定那视频没问题
He owns that place. You sure that video's legit?
看起来没问题
Looks credible.
背景里在播放十点钟的新闻  没问题
They got the 10:00 news on in the background. It checks out.
好吧  我们知道麦克格雷迪
All right, we know McGrady's 911 call
是在10点11分报的警  对吧
came in at 10:11, right?
那家酒吧离麦克格雷迪出事的地方有多远
So how far is the dive bar from where McGrady got hit?
我们刚刚就是从那条路上开回来的  约八公里
We basically just drove that route. It was about 4.8 miles.
我们开得很快  大约用了27分钟
We were driving fast. It took us about 27 minutes.
他不可能十分钟开到
There's no way in hell he made that in ten.
刚刚和技术人员聊了一下
All right. Just talked to the techs.
杀害麦克格雷迪的枪上的血
Blood on the gun that killed McGrady
和昆顿·凯恩的相符
is a match for Quinton Kane.
事实确凿  我们去抓住那个混蛋
Well blood is blood. Let's arrest this prick.
昆顿·凯恩  芝加哥警署  开门
Quinton Kane! Chicago PD! Open up!
昆顿不在
Quinton ain't here.
我们自己来看  在这儿等着
We'll see about that. Wait there.
我有两个孩子  等等
I got two kids! Now hold up!
你们不能就这么闯进来
Y'all can't just come up in here like this.
不用全都进来吧
Don't need to take all y'all.
-厨房安全  -安全
- Kitchen's clear! - Clear.
安全
Clear.
没看到凯恩  但我找到了点东西
No sign of Kane, but I found something.
这可违反了假释条例
That's a parole violation.
直接进监狱  连听证会都不用
Straight to the pokey, no hearing.
不是我的  我不吸毒
It ain't mine. I don't do drugs.
看着我  我们可以帮你
Okay. Look at me. We can help you out,
但我们得知道昆顿在哪里
but we need to know where Quinton is.
你是想让我告我孩子他爸的密
Oh so you want me to rat out the father of my children?
我们是想让你告
No we want you to rat out the guy
那个杀死警察的人的密
who just killed a police officer.
他也有孩子  一个四岁一个六岁  特别可爱
He had kids too. Four and six. Real cute.
快说吧
Come on.
昆顿昨晚来过
Quinton was here last night.
-是来拿枪的  -有人和他在一起吗
- He came to get his guns. - Was he with anyone?
他是和他朋友贝贝一起走的
He left with his friend Bay Bay.
-他们去哪里了  -他没说
- Where did they go? - He didn't say.
但我从没见过昆顿这个样子
But I never seen Quinton act like that before.
-哪个样子  -惊慌失措
- Act like what? - Scared.
他知道你们想为了那个白人警察杀他
He knows y'all are looking to kill him over that white cop.
我让21区的警察监视了每一个
I've got the 21st district tact team sitting on every location
凯恩常去的地方  包括他姨妈  表亲  祖母
Kane's known to frequent. Aunties, cousins, grandmas.
目前为止没有发现
So far, nothing.
我们也是  他把手机和信用卡都扔了
Yeah, us too. Dumped his phone, ran his credit cards.
我们找不到他  除非他用新的一次性手机
He's off the grid, unless he's using a new burner.
你还好吗  我听说博伊特很生气
How you holding up? I hear Voight came down pretty hard.
要是让我说  他有点过了
If you ask me, he was out of line.
我都是照规矩办事
I did everything by the book.
麦克格雷迪想扮演牛仔又不是我的错
It's not my fault McGrady wanted to play cowboy.
如果我是你  我不会把这话说出来
If I were you, I'd keep that to myself.
大家应该不会太想听你的说法
Everyone's a little raw to hear your side of the story.
我们查到凯恩的朋友贝贝的线索了
We got a lead on Kane's boy Bay Bay.
他在南沃尔科特一栋房子里躲着
He was spotted in a stash house on South Wolcott.
我们出发
Let's go.
芝加哥警署  不许动  举起手来
Chicago PD! Don't move! Get your hands up!
所有人举起手来  举起手来
Everybody hands up! Everybody hands up!
-让一让  让一让  -举起手来  举起手来
- Move through, move through. - Hands up! Get up!
把手都举起手来
Let me see 'em up.
把手举起来  快点
Put your hands in the air now! Do it now!
你要去哪儿  把包放下  举起手来
Where you going? Drop the bag, get the hands high.
快点  把包放下  别逼我
Come on. Drop the damn bag, Bay Bay. Don't make me do it.
把包放下  转过身去
Drop the bag! Turn around!
不许看我  给你
Don't look at me. Here you go.
快点  后退走出来  贝贝
Come on. Come on back, Bay Bay.
这是你的房子  你知道该往哪儿走
This your house, you know where to go.
举起手来  脸贴冰箱上  快点  别磨蹭  贝贝
Hands up. Face on the fridge. Come on! Let's do it, Bay Bay!
举起手来  好了
Hands high! There you go!
这是从哪儿来的  打牌赢的吗
Hey, where'd you get this? Playing checkers?
只要你告诉我们昆顿·凯恩在哪儿
If you tell us where Quinton Kane is,
现金的事我们就放过你
we can forget all about that cash, bro.
拜托  我都好久没见过他了
Hey, man. I ain't seen him in days.
我们知道你帮他逃跑了
We know you helped him get away.
听起来你像是在藏匿警察杀手
Yeah, sounds like you were harboring a cop killer to me.
-那我们只好抓你走了  -别碰我
- We taking you in. - Get your hands off me, boy!
你什么毛病
The hell's wrong with you?
-没事了吧  -没事了  我抓住他了
- We good? - Yeah, we good. I got him.
手放背后
Hands behind your back.
我们不是跟你闹着玩的
See we ain't playing with you, bro.
听懂了吗  告诉我昆顿·凯恩在哪里
All right? Talk to me about Quinton Kane right now.
我把他送到了65号和卢米斯大街交叉口
Man, I dropped him off around 65th and Loomis.
-什么时候  -两小时前
- When was that? - Like two hours ago.
你确定  在那之后没见过他
You sure about that? You ain't seen him since?
凯恩15分钟之前打电话来过
Kane called, like, 15 minutes ago.
告诉我让我尽可能搞多点现金
He told me to gather as much cash as possible,
还说他等会儿会打电话告诉我见面地点
and that he would call me back later with the meeting spot.
-他打给你了  -没错
- He called you? - Yeah.
-手机呢  -在我口袋里
- You got phone? - It's in my pocket, bro.
-外套口袋里  -对
- In your jacket? - Yeah.
跪下  快给我跪下
Man, get on your knees. Get down on your knees, baby.
好了
Okay.
看起来像是政府号码
These look like government extensions to me, bro.
凯恩估计有内线
Kane probably has somebody on the inside.
到底怎么回事
What the hell is going on?
汉克  进来  我刚准备打给你
Hank, come on in. I was just about to call you.
你为什么在和昆顿·凯恩联系
Why are you talking to Quinton Kane?
因为我想救他的命
Because I'm trying to save his life.
我联系了凯恩的朋友
Okay, I reached out to some of Kane's associates
告诉他们他得和平投降
and told them that he needed to surrender peacefully.
我说我会帮他  他就给我打电话了
And I said that I would help so he called me.
他在哪里
Where is he?
告诉你之前  我们得先讨论一下流程
Before I share that with you, we need to discuss process.
听我说
Listen to me.
这是警方的行动
This is a police operation.
我们要用自己的方式拿下他
We will take him down our own way.
他不会照你的方式来  我可以向你保证
He won't come in your way. I promise you that.
最好的办法是你和我一起进去
The best approach is for you and me to go in together.
雷  这不是个好主意
Ray, that is not a good idea.
他说自己是无辜的  想要一个公平的审讯
He claims he's innocent, and he wants a fair trial.
昆顿不傻  他知道如果他跑错了地方
Quinton's no dummy. He knows that if he blinks the wrong way,
穿着制服的人会把他
the men in blue are gonna light his ass up
打成筛子  我们刚刚也讨论过
like a Christmas tree, which as we just discussed,
这样对谁来说都不是好事
is no good for anyone.
-你没事吧  -没事
- You all right? - Yeah.
别担心  雷  我陪你一起
Don't worry, Ray. I got your back.
谢谢你啊
Yeah. I appreciate it.
那些拿着枪的乡下小伙子
Those country boys up there with the guns,
他们知道嫌犯又高又瘦  对吗
they know the suspect is tall and thin, right?
应该是的
I believe they do.
没关系
It's cool.
应该在走廊尽头
Should be down at the end of the hall.
好的  我先进去  你跟着我
All right. I'll go in first, you stay behind me.
-手举高一点  -别  昆顿
- Let me see those hands up high. - No! Quinton!
-我没带枪  -手举起来
- I'm not carrying. - Raise your hands!
昆顿  我向你保证  冷静一点
Quinton, you have my word. Calm down now.
好了  昆顿
Come on now, Quinton.
-我向你保证  冷静一点  -转过去
- You have my word. Calm down. - Turn around.
我没有杀警察
I didn't shoot that cop.
我过来不是为了谈这个案子
Yeah, well, I'm not here to discuss the case.
你知道我为什么过来吗
You know why I'm here?
为了保证你活着出去
To make sure you get out of here alive,
保证你有机会说清楚这件事
get a chance to tell your side of the story.
你是说你不相信我吗
Are you saying you don't believe me?
我是说我相信什么不重要
I'm saying it doesn't matter what I believe.
如果你是无辜的  昆顿  把枪放下
If you're innocent, Quinton, put down the gun,
跟我们出去  不会有人伤害你
walk out with us, and no one's gonna hurt you.
不
Nah.
不  还不行  还不行
Nah, not yet. Not yet.
等我出去了再说
I'm gonna wait 'til I'm outside.
这样大家都能看到我很合作
So everybody can see that I'm cooperating.
你很合作吗
You're cooperating?
走吧
Let's go.
你准备好了吗  走吧
Are you ready? Here you go.
我们出来了  别开枪
We're coming out. Don't shoot.
退后  退后
Hey, stand down! Stand down!
都把枪放下  把枪放下
Put your guns-- Put your guns down!
我们全部都要活着走出去
We are all gonna walk out of here alive.
我们每一个人
Every one of us.
你们都把武器放下
Put your weapon down.
好了  昆顿  你也是
All right, Quinton. You too.
冷静  昆顿  有我在
Calm down, Quinton. I got it.
-好了  -我向你保证  昆顿
- Come on. - You got my word, Quinton.
你想平平安安地走出去吗
You want to walk out of here in one piece?
好了  你看看
Come on. Look at this.
-我跟你保证过  -快  放聪明点
- You got my word. - Come on. Be smart.
好了
Come on, man.
走吧
There you go.
好了  过来吧
There you go! Come on in.
转过去  转过去
All right, turn around. Turn around.
-手举起来  -我跟你保证过
- Put your hands up. - You got my word.
我们走吧  走
Let's get out of here. Come on.
-谢谢  雷  -谢谢
- Thanks, Ray. - Thank you.
今晚  芝加哥可以安全一点了
Tonight, Chicago sleeps safer.
昆顿·凯恩因为谋杀一名
Quinton Kane is in custody for the murder
芝加哥警察之死而被收监
of a Chicago police officer.
我跟肖恩·麦克格雷迪警长关系很好
I was very close with Sergeant Sean McGrady.
他就是我们警察想要成为的样子
He was everything that we as police strive to be.
他诚实守信  勇于奉献
He was honest. He was dedicated.
英勇果敢
He was courageous.
我们永远不能忘记麦克格雷迪警长的牺牲
We must never forget Sergeant McGrady's sacrifice.
谢谢大家
Thank you.
你派了一个战术小队过去还不告诉我
You sent in a tactical team without telling me?
-我们抓到人了  -本来就已经抓住了
- We got our man. - We already had our man.
你只需要获得他的信任
You just needed to get the credit.
我们抓的是杀警察的人
Well, I needed to make sure we apprehended a cop killer,
我需要确保你和雷活着出来
and that we got you and Ray out of there alive.
这是我唯一的任务
That was my only agenda.
是这样就好  因为在那里的时候
Well, that's good to know, 'cause for a minute there,
感觉像有私仇
it felt personal.
走快一点吧
Pick up your feet, please.
谢谢你们
Thank you.
好的  你先
All right. You first.
安妮
Anne.
我一会儿就来
I'll be just a minute.
有任何需要帮忙的  你或者孩子
If there's anything that you need, you, the kids,
打电话给我
please call me.
谢谢你  我很感激
Thanks. I appreciate that.
那天  对不起啊
And I'm--I'm sorry about the other day.
我不是存心针对你
I didn't mean to be so abrupt.
-没关系  -我只是...
- It's all right. - I just--
麦克真的很喜欢你
Mac really liked you.
他总是说你有多聪明
He always said how smart you were.
很高兴知道这些
That's nice to know.
有任何需要  告诉我
Anything you need, let me know.
其实真有一件事我想跟你说
Actually there is something I would like to address.
尽管说
Yeah. Name it.
现在看来好像毫无意义  但我放不下
It seems so meaningless now, but I can't let it go.
麦克有一天晚上从社区中心回来
Mac came home from Community Play one night...
特别沮丧
really upset.
会计指责麦克偷钱
The treasurer accused Mac of stealing money.
这么严重啊
That's terrible.
你记得那个人的名字吗
Do you remember the guy's name?
迈克·亚当斯
Mike Adams.
有几笔账是现金交易
There were some checks made out to cash.
好像是麦克格雷迪警长负责的
It looked like Sergeant McGrady was responsible.
你觉得他在偷钱吗
You thought he was stealing money?
-是的  -丢了多少钱
- Yes. - How much money was missing?
大概一万
Close to $10,000.
我跟他说我们会报警
I told him we were going to file a police report.
聚会那晚你们就是因为这个吵架吗
Is that what you were fighting about the night of the party?
发生了这么多事
I assume after everything that's happened
你应该会让这事就这么过去吧
that you're gonna let this go now?
当然
Of course.
特别是现在  案子已经结了
Especially now, after the case is closed.
凶手已经归案
Killer's in custody.
新闻说他们在麦克格雷迪的枪上发现了他的血迹
You know I read they found his blood on McGrady's gun?
那事情就简单了
Sounds like a no-brainer.
谢谢
Thanks.
我是厄普顿警察  情报组
Detective Upton, Intelligence.
今天我手上有两个案子
I have two cases on the docket today.
我发现了重要线索  我们要马上谈一下
I found something important. We need to talk about it now.
收到你的留言了
Got your message.
你来看看这个
You'll wanna check this out.
病理室的登记表
Okay, an ISP sign-in sheet.
这是麦克格雷迪的签名
That's McGrady's signature.
所以呢
So?
两个月前昆顿·凯恩因为醉驾被抓
Quinton Kane was popped for a DUI two months ago.
他的血液放在证据库里
His blood's been sitting in an evidence cooler.
其中有一瓶不见了
One of the vials is missing.
你是说麦克格雷迪偷了凯恩的血吗
You're saying McGrady stole Kane's blood?
-对  -为什么
- Yep. - Why?
好嫁祸他
So he could frame him.
嫁祸他谋杀他
Frame him for his own murder?
不  是把自己的自杀嫁祸给他
No. Frame him for his own suicide.
我听说葬礼今天举行
I hear the funeral is today.
对  一小时后
Yep. Starts in an hour.
麦克格雷迪肯定会风风光光走
I'm sure McGrady is gonna get a hell of a send-off.
那些风笛声一直让我起鸡皮疙瘩
Those bagpipes always make me tremble.
《回家》
"Coming Home."
大家都以为是苏格兰的
Everyone thinks it's Scottish.
其实是美国黑人灵歌
It's actually an African-American spiritual.
这我真不知道
I didn't know that.
事情永远不是表面看起来那样
Things are never what they seem.
我听到谣言说麦克格雷迪在
You know, I heard a rumor that McGrady was stealing cash
从社区中心偷钱
from Community Play.
我第一次听说
That's news to me.
这只是我的想法  思考
I'm just thinking aloud here. Musing.
我可能是对的  也可能是错的
Maybe I'm right, maybe I'm wrong.
麦克格雷迪走投无路  知道自己快暴露了
McGrady's circling the drain, knows he's about to be exposed.
所以把自己的自杀嫁祸给了一个黑人毒贩
So he frames a black drug dealer for his own suicide.
他成了英雄  他的妻子和孩子
He goes out a hero, and his wife and kids,
他们可以得到一笔不菲的抚恤金
they get to collect a healthy pension.
听上去很离谱
That sounds far-fetched.
我还听说有一段
I also heard there's a surveillance video
凯恩在一个酒吧喝威士忌的录像
of Kane drinking whiskey at a bar damn near the same time
跟麦克格雷迪中枪是同一时间
McGrady got shot.
当然  是直到昨晚
Until last night, that is.
有人闯进酒吧时
When someone broke into the bar,
那段录像不见了
and the video disappears.
现在轮到我思考了
Yeah, well, now it's my turn to muse.
你不在乎凯恩  根本不在乎
You don't care about Kane. I mean, not even a little.
他是个惯犯
He's an old-fashioned criminal.
对开明的议员不懂尊重
Doesn't believe in paying tribute to enlightened aldermen.
对
No.
凯恩不在了
And with Kane gone,
会有别人占领他的地盘
another banger's going to take over that territory,
在正确的帮助和引导之下
and I think with the correct help, guidance,
他会知道投资自己的选区是明智的
he'll come to understand the wisdom of investing in his ward.
或许你说得对吧
Maybe you're right.
但这不是说我会平白无故为你保密
But that doesn't mean my silence is free.
雷啊雷  你想要什么
Ray, Ray. What is it that you want?
我想要什么  我想要什么
What do I want? What do I want?
我想要你记住
I want you to remember.
我在帮你
I'm doing you a favor.
就这个  我只要这个
That's it. That's all I'm asking.
我很快会再跟你聊  汉克
I'm gonna talk to you soon, Hank.
还用说
No doubt.
应该有更多像麦克一样的警察
There should be more cops like Mac.
是啊  我们以前经常在社区中心打牌
Yeah. We used to play horse over at Community Play.
我一直都赢他
I always kicked his ass.
你知道他是故意让你赢的
Well, you know he let you win.
我就是想让他这么想
Exactly what I wanted him to think.
好吧
All right.
厄普顿还好吧
How's Upton dealing with all of this?
不知道  她要接受很多
I'm not sure. She keeps a lot in.
我们都是  对吧  这是警察工作的一部分
We all do, right? It's part of the job.
米娅的电话吗
Call from Mia, huh?
-她真不是跟你闹着玩的  -喂
- She ain't playing with you. - Hello?
什么时候
When?
一小时后我可以过去
Yeah, I can be there in an hour.
一个人养孩子不容易
Not easy raising kids on your own.
孩子们  你们上楼好吗
Hey, guys. Can you go upstairs, please?
她很坚强
She's a strong woman.
她有很多朋友
She's got lots of friends.
如果有人能做到  她肯定能
If anyone can pull it off, she can.
海莉  海莉  等等
Hailey. Hailey, hold up.
我知道咖啡和让麦克格雷迪一个人行动的事
So I know I came down kind of hard on you about this coffee thing,
我对你太过分了
letting McGrady go in alone.
-我现在都明白了  -其实
- Well, I get it now, so. - It's not really
你想跟我说的不是这个吧
what you want to talk to me about though, is it?
你跟我要统一意见
You and me gotta get on the same page.
我们要么把证据公开
Either we disclose this evidence,
要么带进坟墓
or we take it to the grave.
等等  大家都把他当英雄
Wait. Doesn't it bother you
难道你就不觉得不舒服吗
that everyone looks at him like he's a hero?
我也不舒服
Yeah. It bothers me.
麦克格雷迪是个好人
McGrady was a good man.
好警察  是的
Good cop? Sure.
好人  不是  他不是好人
Good man? No. Not so much.
他把自己的积蓄都赌光了
He gambled away his savings,
他出轨
he cheated on Anne,
还想毁掉我的事业
tried to sabotage my career.
我每次想升职的时候
Every time I was up for a promotion,
那个混蛋都尽可能妨碍我
son of a bitch did his best to jam me up.
我知道
I know.
他并不完美
He wasn't perfect.
但他是个好警察  这点我确定
But he was a good cop. I know that for sure,
因为我见过他出警
'cause I saw him in action.
枪林弹雨的时候  我看到过他行动
I watched what he did when the bullets were flying,
相信我...
and believe me--
海莉  他有两个孩子
Hailey, he's got two little kids.
你想想事情败露后他们会怎么样
Think about what happens to them if this comes out.
他们就只有他的遗产
All they have is his legacy.
还有还他抚恤金
And his pension.
你要为一个因为几公斤可卡因
I mean, you want to blow all of that over some jackass
就杀了一家三口的混蛋  毁了这一切吗
who mowed down a family of three over a couple kilos of coke?
这座城市现在需要一个警察英雄
This city could use a hero in blue right now.
需要一个受人敬仰的人
Someone the people could admire.
即使他是个骗子
Even if he's a fraud?
好
Okay.
带到坟墓
To the grave.
谢谢你终于接我的电话了
Thanks for finally taking my call.
我有点忙
I've been a bit busy.
我找你的时候你不能忙
Yeah, well, you don't get to be busy.
也不能没空  你明白了吗
Or unavailable. You understand?
我上周告诉过你
Like I told you last week,
你是我的
I own you.
你姐姐开车带着你的小侄子
The second your sister got popped for that DUI
醉驾被抓
with your little nephew in the backseat,
你想偷偷处理掉的时候
you tried to make it all go away,
你生气或者不方便的权利
your right to being agitated or inconvenienced
就没有了
came to an abrupt end.
你伪造了官方报告
You falsified official reports.
销毁了证据
Buried evidence.
如果不是我开明
Hell, if I weren't so open-minded,
你可能因为这个进监狱的
you could go to jail over this.
你想要什么
What do you want?
你的眼睛  你的耳朵
Your eyes. Your ears.
不行  绝对不行
No. Uh-uh. No.
我不是内奸
I'm not a rat, man.
不是吗  真的吗
No? You don't think so?
不是
No.
那是我内务部的朋友
That's my dear friend from IAD.
但如果你不想玩...
But if you don't want to play...
我可以马上叫他来
I just call his cranky ass right now.
等等
Hang it up.
这就对了  决定得好
There you go, son. That's a good decision.
我们说说细节吧
Now let's talk details.